{
  "flashcards": [
    {
      "id": 1,
      "category": "spanish",
      "subcategory": "cantUnderstand",
      "front": "The slower you talk, the better I can understand you.",
      "back": "Cuanto más lento hables, mejor te entenderé.",
      "rank": 4.1,
      "whenCreated": "2023-01-29 17:43:22"
    },
    {
      "id": 2,
      "category": "spanish",
      "subcategory": "wantToLearn",
      "front": "How to you say the word \"above\" in Spanish?",
      "back": "¿Cómo se dice la palabra \"above\" en español?",
      "rank": 5,
      "whenCreated": "2023-01-29 16:46:35"
    },
    {
      "category": "spanish",
      "subcategory": "cantUnderstand",
      "front": "I'm sorry, I don't understand you. / I still can't understand you.",
      "back": "Lo siento, no te entiendo. / Todavía no puedo entenderte.",
      "rank": 4.9,
      "whenCreated": "2023-01-29 19:40:48",
      "id": 3
    },
    {
      "category": "spanish",
      "subcategory": "",
      "front": "What time is it?",
      "back": "¿Qué hora será?",
      "rank": 4.2,
      "whenCreated": "2023-01-29 19:40:48",
      "id": 4
    },
    {
      "category": "spanish",
      "subcategory": "cantUnderstand",
      "front": "My Spanish isn't good enough to understand you.",
      "back": "Mi español no es suficiente para entenderte.",
      "rank": 4.95,
      "whenCreated": "2023-01-29 19:40:48",
      "id": 5
    },
    {
      "category": "spanish",
      "subcategory": "",
      "front": "I'll do it.",
      "back": "Lo haré.",
      "rank": 2.5,
      "whenCreated": "2023-01-29 19:40:48",
      "id": 6
    },
    {
      "category": "spanish",
      "subcategory": "",
      "front": "I need to get some more coffee.",
      "back": "Necesito tomar un poco más de café.",
      "rank": 3.8,
      "whenCreated": "2023-01-29 19:47:48",
      "id": 7
    },
    {
      "category": "spanish",
      "subcategory": "cantUnderstand",
      "front": "Could you repeat what you just said?",
      "back": "¿Podrías repetir lo que acabas de decir?",
      "rank": 4.5,
      "whenCreated": "2023-01-29 19:47:48",
      "id": 8
    },
    {
      "category": "spanish",
      "subcategory": "",
      "front": "I forgot something",
      "back": "me olvidé de algo",
      "rank": 3.8,
      "whenCreated": "2023-01-29 19:54:37",
      "id": 9
    },
    {
      "category": "spanish",
      "subcategory": "",
      "front": "We'll see each other tomorrow.",
      "back": "Nos vemos mañana.",
      "rank": 2.5,
      "whenCreated": "2023-01-29 19:54:37",
      "id": 11
    },
    {
      "category": "spanish",
      "subcategory": "",
      "front": "I think this feature will be hard to program.",
      "back": "Creo que esta función será difícil de programar.",
      "rank": 2.5,
      "whenCreated": "2023-01-29 19:56:32",
      "id": 12
    },
    {
      "category": "spanish",
      "subcategory": "cantUnderstand",
      "front": "Sorry, you spoke so quickly, I didn't understand.",
      "back": "Lo siento, hablaste tan rápido que no entendí.",
      "rank": 4.5,
      "whenCreated": "2023-01-29 19:59:48",
      "id": 13
    },
    {
      "category": "spanish",
      "subcategory": "",
      "front": "It is time for lunch.",
      "back": "Es hora de almorzar.",
      "rank": 4.1,
      "whenCreated": "2023-01-29 20:01:56",
      "id": 14
    },
    {
      "category": "spanish",
      "subcategory": "wantToLearn",
      "front": "What does the word \"tampoco\" mean?",
      "back": "¿Qué significa la palabra \"tampoco\"?",
      "rank": 5,
      "whenCreated": "2023-01-29 20:03:29",
      "id": 15
    },
    {
      "category": "spanish",
      "subcategory": "wantToLearn",
      "front": "I have a question.",
      "back": "Tengo una pregunta.",
      "rank": 4.8,
      "whenCreated": "2023-01-29 20:34:27",
      "id": 16
    },
    {
      "category": "spanish",
      "subcategory": "cantUnderstand",
      "front": "What did you say after the word nnn?",
      "back": "¿Qué dijiste después de la palabra nnn?",
      "rank": 4.5,
      "whenCreated": "2023-01-29 20:39:19",
      "id": 17
    },
    {
      "category": "spanish",
      "subcategory": "cantUnderstand",
      "front": "That's what I thought you said.",
      "back": "Eso es lo que pensé que habías dicho.",
      "rank": 4.2,
      "whenCreated": "2023-01-29 20:39:19",
      "id": 18
    },
    {
      "category": "spanish",
      "subcategory": "cantUnderstand",
      "front": "I didn't understand the word nnn.",
      "back": "No entendí la palabra nnn.",
      "rank": 4.6,
      "whenCreated": "2023-01-29 20:40:41",
      "id": 19
    },
    {
      "category": "spanish",
      "subcategory": "cantUnderstand",
      "front": "What does it mean?",
      "back": "¿Qué significa?",
      "rank": 4.7,
      "whenCreated": "2023-01-29 20:41:43",
      "id": 20
    },
    {
      "category": "spanish",
      "subcategory": "",
      "front": "We can start with a number of questions that I have.",
      "back": "Podemos comenzar con una serie de preguntas que tengo.",
      "rank": 2.5,
      "whenCreated": "2023-01-29 20:42:38",
      "id": 21
    },
    {
      "category": "spanish",
      "subcategory": "",
      "front": "I have to answer the door. I will be right back.",
      "back": "Tengo que abrir la puerta. Ya vuelvo.",
      "rank": 3.9,
      "whenCreated": "2023-01-29 20:44:02",
      "id": 22
    },
    {
      "category": "spanish",
      "subcategory": "",
      "front": "we should do that as early as possible",
      "back": "deberíamos hacerlo lo antes posible",
      "rank": 2.5,
      "whenCreated": "2023-01-29 20:48:14",
      "id": 23
    },
    {
      "category": "spanish",
      "subcategory": "",
      "front": "see you tomorrow",
      "back": "Hasta mañana",
      "rank": 2.5,
      "whenCreated": "2023-01-29 20:49:44",
      "id": 24
    },
    {
      "category": "spanish",
      "subcategory": "",
      "front": "we should do that as fast as possible",
      "back": "deberíamos hacerlo lo más rápido posible",
      "rank": 2.5,
      "whenCreated": "2023-01-29 20:50:47",
      "id": 25
    },
    {
      "category": "spanish",
      "subcategory": "cantUnderstand",
      "front": "Could you repeat that?",
      "back": "¿Peudes repetirlo?",
      "rank": 4.8,
      "whenCreated": "2023-01-29 20:53:03",
      "id": 26
    },
    {
      "category": "spanish",
      "subcategory": "",
      "front": "I think that is true.",
      "back": "Penso que es verdad.",
      "rank": 2.5,
      "whenCreated": "2023-01-29 20:55:06",
      "id": 27
    },
    {
      "category": "spanish",
      "subcategory": "",
      "front": "I think that is false.",
      "back": "Creo que es falso.",
      "rank": 2.5,
      "whenCreated": "2023-01-29 20:55:06",
      "id": 28
    },
    {
      "category": "spanish",
      "subcategory": "",
      "front": "What do you think?",
      "back": "¿Qué piensas?",
      "rank": 3.9,
      "whenCreated": "2023-01-29 20:56:24",
      "id": 29
    },
    {
      "category": "spanish",
      "subcategory": "",
      "front": "Are you guys already starting?",
      "back": "¿Empezáis ya?",
      "rank": 2.5,
      "whenCreated": "2023-01-29 20:57:52",
      "id": 30
    },
    {
      "category": "spanish",
      "subcategory": "",
      "front": "Do you understand the difference?",
      "back": "¿Entiendes la diferencia?",
      "rank": 2.5,
      "whenCreated": "2023-01-29 20:58:54",
      "id": 31
    },
    {
      "category": "spanish",
      "subcategory": "",
      "front": "This is going to take a long time.",
      "back": "Esto va a llevar mucho tiempo.",
      "rank": 2.5,
      "whenCreated": "2023-01-29 21:09:05",
      "id": 32
    },
    {
      "category": "spanish",
      "subcategory": "",
      "front": "Unfortunately not.",
      "back": "Lamentablemente no.",
      "rank": 2.5,
      "whenCreated": "2023-01-29 21:37:28",
      "id": 33
    },
    {
      "category": "spanish",
      "subcategory": "",
      "front": "It looks like your live coding showed the studens the inicial steps in case they want to integrate Auth0 into their final projects.",
      "back": "Parece que tu live coding les mostró a los estudiantes los pasos iniciales en caso de que quisieran integrar Auth0 en su final projects.",
      "rank": 2.5,
      "whenCreated": "2023-02-01 19:19:28",
      "id": 34
    },
    {
      "category": "spanish",
      "subcategory": "",
      "front": "If you had told me, I could have avoided this mistake.",
      "back": "Si me lo hubieras dicho habría podido evitar este error.",
      "rank": 2.5,
      "whenCreated": "2023-02-18 21:09:00",
      "id": 35
    },
    {
      "category": "spanish",
      "subcategory": "",
      "front": "you all can check in the documentation",
      "back": "podáis revisar en la documentation",
      "rank": 2.5,
      "whenCreated": "2023-02-20 14:18:55",
      "id": 37
    },
    {
      "category": "spanish",
      "subcategory": "",
      "front": "instead",
      "back": "en vez",
      "rank": 2.5,
      "whenCreated": "2023-02-24 21:52:35",
      "id": 38
    },
    {
      "category": "spanish",
      "subcategory": "",
      "front": "let's keep it simple",
      "back": "vamos a hacerlo simple",
      "rank": 2.5,
      "whenCreated": "2023-02-24 22:27:10",
      "id": 39
    },
    {
      "category": "spanish",
      "subcategory": "",
      "front": "what I'm going to do is",
      "back": "lo que voy a hacer es",
      "rank": 2.5,
      "whenCreated": "2023-02-24 22:27:10",
      "id": 40
    },
    {
      "category": "spanish",
      "subcategory": "",
      "front": "What were you saying?",
      "back": "¿Qué decías ?",
      "rank": 2.5,
      "whenCreated": "2023-02-24 22:27:10",
      "id": 41
    },
    {
      "category": "spanish",
      "subcategory": "",
      "front": "He said he would go.",
      "back": "Él dijo que iría.",
      "rank": 2.5,
      "whenCreated": "2023-02-24 22:34:49",
      "id": 43
    },
    {
      "category": "spanish",
      "subcategory": "",
      "front": "Working hard made Jack what he is.",
      "back": "El trabajo duro definió a Jack.",
      "rank": 2.5,
      "whenCreated": "2023-02-24 22:34:49",
      "id": 44
    },
    {
      "category": "spanish",
      "subcategory": "",
      "front": "She described her life as a box full of surprises.",
      "back": "Ella definió su vida como una caja de sorpresa.",
      "rank": 2.5,
      "whenCreated": "2023-02-24 22:34:49",
      "id": 45
    },
    {
      "category": "spanish",
      "subcategory": "",
      "front": "pr. las llaves",
      "back": "JAW-vays",
      "rank": 2.5,
      "whenCreated": "2023-02-24 22:34:49",
      "id": 46
    },
    {
      "category": "spanish",
      "subcategory": "",
      "front": "it's incredible",
      "back": "es increíble",
      "rank": 2.5,
      "whenCreated": "2023-02-24 22:44:28",
      "id": 47
    },
    {
      "category": "spanish",
      "subcategory": "",
      "front": "pr. yo voy a copiar",
      "back": "[joe boy]",
      "rank": 2.5,
      "whenCreated": "2023-02-24 22:44:28",
      "id": 48
    },
    {
      "category": "spanish",
      "subcategory": "",
      "front": "so i'm going to copy it",
      "back": "así que voy a copiarlo",
      "rank": 2.5,
      "whenCreated": "2023-02-24 23:07:18",
      "id": 49
    },
    {
      "category": "spanish",
      "subcategory": "",
      "front": "I have to whole weekend to practice",
      "back": "tengo todo el fin de semana para practicar",
      "rank": 2.5,
      "whenCreated": "2023-02-24 23:07:18",
      "id": 50
    },
    {
      "category": "spanish",
      "subcategory": "",
      "front": "pr. es un placer",
      "back": "plah-/th/er",
      "rank": 2.5,
      "whenCreated": "2023-02-24 23:07:18",
      "id": 51
    },
    {
      "category": "spanish",
      "subcategory": "",
      "front": "I want to finish this.",
      "back": "Quiero terminar esto.",
      "rank": 2.5,
      "whenCreated": "2023-02-24 23:07:18",
      "id": 52
    },
    {
      "category": "spanish",
      "subcategory": "",
      "front": "and for that reason",
      "back": "y por esa razón",
      "rank": 2.5,
      "whenCreated": "2023-02-24 23:07:18",
      "id": 53
    },
    {
      "category": "spanish",
      "subcategory": "",
      "front": "pr. he trabajado en esto",
      "back": "/H/ado",
      "rank": 2.5,
      "whenCreated": "2023-02-24 23:07:18",
      "id": 54
    },
    {
      "category": "spanish",
      "subcategory": "",
      "front": "for a long time",
      "back": "durante mucho tiempo",
      "rank": 2.5,
      "whenCreated": "2023-02-24 23:07:19",
      "id": 55
    },
    {
      "category": "spanish",
      "subcategory": "",
      "front": "that is populated with objects",
      "back": "que está poblado de objetos [/ch/ay-tohs]",
      "rank": 2.5,
      "whenCreated": "2023-02-24 23:36:09",
      "id": 56
    },
    {
      "category": "spanish",
      "subcategory": "",
      "front": "if I try to see",
      "back": "si yo trato de ver",
      "rank": 2.5,
      "whenCreated": "2023-02-24 23:36:09",
      "id": 57
    },
    {
      "category": "spanish",
      "subcategory": "",
      "front": "that even though",
      "back": "que aunque",
      "rank": 2.5,
      "whenCreated": "2023-02-24 23:36:09",
      "id": 58
    },
    {
      "category": "spanish",
      "subcategory": "",
      "front": "tal como lo definí",
      "back": "as i defined it",
      "rank": 2.5,
      "whenCreated": "2023-02-24 23:36:09",
      "id": 59
    },
    {
      "category": "spanish",
      "subcategory": "",
      "front": "a box",
      "back": "una casilla",
      "rank": 2.5,
      "whenCreated": "2023-02-25 12:32:27",
      "id": 60
    },
    {
      "category": "spanish",
      "subcategory": "",
      "front": "You should have told it to me sooner.",
      "back": "Debiste habérmelo dicho antes.",
      "rank": 2.5,
      "whenCreated": "2023-02-25 12:49:47",
      "id": 61
    },
    {
      "category": "spanish",
      "subcategory": "",
      "front": "We need to get started.",
      "back": "Tenemos que arrancar.",
      "rank": 2.5,
      "whenCreated": "2023-02-25 13:14:18",
      "id": 62
    },
    {
      "category": "spanish",
      "subcategory": "",
      "front": "I'm going to delete the href property here",
      "back": "voy a borrar acá la propiedad href [ACH-ay-ref]",
      "rank": 2.5,
      "whenCreated": "2023-02-25 13:17:27",
      "id": 63
    },
    {
      "category": "spanish",
      "subcategory": "",
      "front": "before an underscore",
      "back": "antes un guión bajo [ggee-OHN BAH-/ch/oh, hard g]",
      "rank": 2.5,
      "whenCreated": "2023-02-25 13:25:55",
      "id": 64
    },
    {
      "category": "spanish",
      "subcategory": "",
      "front": "dollar sign and keys",
      "back": "signo de dólar y llaves [SEEG-noh]",
      "rank": 2.5,
      "whenCreated": "2023-02-25 13:27:59",
      "id": 65
    },
    {
      "category": "spanish",
      "subcategory": "",
      "front": "even though",
      "back": "a pesar de que",
      "rank": 2.5,
      "whenCreated": "2023-02-25 13:58:54",
      "id": 66
    },
    {
      "category": "spanish",
      "subcategory": "",
      "front": "I'm going to choose",
      "back": "voy a escoger",
      "rank": 2.5,
      "whenCreated": "2023-02-25 13:59:26",
      "id": 67
    },
    {
      "category": "spanish",
      "subcategory": "",
      "front": "my app doesn't know exactly where I clicked",
      "back": "mi aplicación no sabe exactamente dónde hice clic",
      "rank": 2.5,
      "whenCreated": "2023-02-25 14:00:47",
      "id": 68
    },
    {
      "category": "spanish",
      "subcategory": "",
      "front": "to be maintained throughout life",
      "back": "que se mantenga a lo largo de la vida",
      "rank": 2.5,
      "whenCreated": "2023-02-25 14:02:36",
      "id": 69
    }
  ]
}